<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<db>
  <code id="0x1" name="APC_INDEX_MISMATCH">
    <description>
      Indicates that there is a mismatch in the APC state index.
    </description>
    <p1>The address of the system call.</p1>
    <p2>The value of the following: Thread->ApcStateIndex &lt;&lt; 8 | Previous ApcStateIndex</p2>
    <p3>The value of Thread->KernelApcDisable</p3>
    <p4>The value of the previous KernelApcDisable</p4>
  </code>
  <code id="0x2" name="DEVICE_QUEUE_NOT_BUSY" />
  <code id="0x3" name="INVALID_AFFINITY_SET" />
  <code id="0x4" name="INVALID_DATA_ACCESS_TRAP" />
  <code id="0x5" name="INVALID_PROCESS_ATTACH_ATTEMPT" />
  <code id="0x6" name="INVALID_PROCESS_DETACH_ATTEMPT" />
  <code id="0x7" name="INVALID_SOFTWARE_INTERRUPT" />
  <code id="0x8" name="IRQL_NOT_DISPATCH_LEVEL" />
  <code id="0x9" name="IRQL_NOT_GREATER_OR_EQUAL" />
  <code id="0xa" name="IRQL_NOT_LESS_OR_EQUAL">
    <description>
      Indicates that kernel-mode code accessed paged memory at DISPATCH_LEVEL or above.
    </description>
    <p1>Memory referenced.</p1>
    <p2>IRQL at the time.</p2>
    <p3>0: Read, 1: Write.</p3>
    <p4>Address which referenced memory.</p4>
  </code>
  <code id="0xb" name="NO_EXCEPTION_HANDLING_SUPPORT" />
  <code id="0xc" name="MAXIMUM_WAIT_OBJECTS_EXCEEDED">
    <description>
      Indicates that the current thread exceeded the permitted number of wait objects.
    </description>
  </code>
  <code id="0xd" name="MUTEX_LEVEL_NUMBER_VIOLATION" />
  <code id="0xe" name="NO_USER_MODE_CONTEXT" />
  <code id="0xf" name="SPIN_LOCK_ALREADY_OWNED">
    <description>
      Indicates that a request for a spin lock was initiated when the spin lock was already owned.
    </description>
  </code>
  <code id="0x10" name="SPIN_LOCK_NOT_OWNED" />
  <code id="0x11" name="THREAD_NOT_MUTEX_OWNER" />
  <code id="0x12" name="TRAP_CAUSE_UNKNOWN">
    <description>
      Indicates that an unknown exception has occurred.
    </description>
    <p1>The unexcepted interrupt.</p1>
    <p2>The unknown floating-point exception.</p2>
    <p3>The enabled and asserted status bits.</p3>
    <p4>Reserved.</p4>
  </code>
  <code id="0x13" name="EMPTY_THREAD_REAPER_LIST" />
  <code id="0x14" name="CREATE_DELETE_LOCK_NOT_LOCKED" />
  <code id="0x15" name="LAST_CHANCE_CALLED_FROM_KMODE" />
  <code id="0x16" name="CID_HANDLE_CREATION" />
  <code id="0x17" name="CID_HANDLE_DELETION" />
  <code id="0x18" name="REFERENCE_BY_POINTER">
    <description>
      Indicates that the reference count of an object is illegal for the current state of the object.
    </description>
    <p1>Object type of the object whose reference count is being lowered.</p1>
    <p2>Object whose reference count is being lowered.</p2>
    <p3>Reserved.</p3>
    <p4>Reserved.</p4>
  </code>
  <code id="0x19" name="BAD_POOL_HEADER">
    <description>
      Indicates that a pool header is corrupt.
    </description>
  </code>
  <code id="0x1a" name="MEMORY_MANAGEMENT">
    <description>
      Indicates that a severe memory management error occurred.
    </description>
  </code>
  <code id="0x50" name="PAGE_FAULT_IN_NONPAGED_AREA">
    <description>
      Indicates that invalid system memory has been referenced.
    </description>
    <p1>Memory address referenced.</p1>
    <p2>0: Read, 1: Write.</p2>
    <p3>Address that referenced memory.</p3>
    <p4>Reserved.</p4>
  </code>
  <code id="0x5d" name="UNSUPPORTED_PROCESSOR">
    <description>
      Indicates that the computer is attempting to run Windows on an unsupported processor.
    </description>
  </code>
  <code id="0x93" name="INVALID_KERNEL_HANDLE">
    <description>
      Indicates that an invalid or protected handle was passed to NtClose.
    </description>
    <p1>The handle that was passed to NtClose.</p1>
    <p2>0: The caller tried to close a protected handle, 1: The caller tried to close an invalid handle.</p2>
  </code>
  <code id="0x98" name="END_OF_NT_EVALUATION_PERIOD">
    <description>
      Indicates that the trial period for Windows has ended.
    </description>
    <p1>The low 32-bits of the expiration date.</p1>
    <p2>The high 32-bits of the expiration date.</p2>
    <p3>Reserved.</p3>
    <p4>Reserved.</p4>
  </code>
  <code id="0x9a" name="SYSTEM_LICENSE_VIOLATION">
    <description>
      Indicates that the Windows EULA has been violated.
    </description>
    <p1>
0x0: Offline product type changes have been attempted.
0x1: Offline changes to the Windows evaluation time period have been attempted.
0x2: The setup key could not be opened.
0x3: The setup mode could not be detected.
0x4: The SystemPrefix value from the setup key is missing.
0x5: Offline changes to the number of licensed processors have been attempted.
0x6: The ProductOptions key could not be opened.
0x7: The ProductType value could not be read.
0x8: Change Notify on ProductOptions failed.
0x9: Change Notify on SystemPrefix failed.
0xa: An NTW system was converted to an NTS system.
0xb: The reference of the setup key failed.
0xc: The reference of the product options key failed.
0xd: The attempt to open ProductOptions in the worker thread failed.
0xf: The attempt to open the setup key failed.
0x10: A failure occurred in the setup key worker thread.
0x11: A failure occurred in the product options key worker thread.
0x12: Unable to open the LicenseInfoSuites key for the suite.
0x13: Unable to query the LicenseInfoSuites key for the suite.
0x14: Unable to allocate memory.
0x15: Unable to reset the ConcurrentLimit value for the suite key.
0x16: Unable to open the license key for a suite product.
0x17: Unable to reset the ConcurrentLimit value for a suite product.
0x18: Unable to start the Change Notify for the LicenseInfoSuites.
0x19: A suite is running on a system that must be PDC.
0x1a: A failure occurred when enumerating the suites.
0x1b: Changes to the policy cache were attempted.
    </p1>
  </code>
  <code id="0xfc" name="ATTEMPTED_EXECUTE_OF_NOEXECUTE_MEMORY">
    <description>Indicates that an attempt was made to execute non-executable memory.</description>
    <p1>The address whose execution was attempted.</p1>
    <p2>The contents of the page table entry (PTE).</p2>
    <p3>Reserved.</p3>
    <p4>Reserved.</p4>
  </code>
  <code id="0xfd" name="DIRTY_NOWRITE_PAGES_CONGESTION">
    <description>Indicates that there are no free pages available to continue basic system operations.</description>
    <p1>Total number of dirty pages.</p1>
    <p2>Number of non-writeable dirty pages.</p2>
    <p3>Reserved.</p3>
    <p4>Most recently modified write-error status.</p4>
  </code>
  <code id="0xdeaddead" name="MANUALLY_INITIATED_CRASH">
    <description>
      Indicates that the user deliberately initiated a crash dump.
    </description>
  </code>
</db>